VIKTOR POSZT

FULL STACK DEVELOPER





Contact

% +36202613069

www.linkedin.com/in/viktor-

poszt/

github.com/Fonxy666

Self Definition

As a child, it was hard for me to choose between two different career paths: becoming a programmer or an architect. Both of them attracted me very much, but finally I decided to learn architecture and then I worked in this field for a year. As during this time I realized that it's not really my way, I re-joined Mercedes Benz and worked there for 5 years. After a year, I was promoted and became a Team Leader. However, as I aimed to reach something more and make my childhood dreams come true, I started looking at programming schools and finally due to a friend's recommendation, I joined Codecool's Full Stack Developer course. I love understanding how things work and enjoy creating with programming. My goal is to gain deep knowledge in my chosen programming languages and contribute to software development with my unique perspectives. Ready to dive into the tech world, I'm eager to learn and grow.

Strength

I am adaptable and optimistic and I excel in problem-solving thanks to my creative mindset. I have strong team management and presentation skills due to my experiences gained in manufacturing and in Codecool. Proficient in C#, .NET, Javascript/React, Express.js, and databases.

Mentor Opinion

"He has the ability to comprehend sophisticated concepts, and after understanding them he can quickly implement what he has learned in a live project. By now he managed to build himself up in the field of IT to a level where he would make a great addition to any team as a Junior Developer."

— Erik Rabóczki, mentor



Hard Skills



























Recent Projects

SOLARWATCH

https://github.com/CodecoolGlobal/solarwatch-api-1-csharp-Fonxy666

Solarwatch application is a solo-project, using C# as a backend, React as a frontend, and PostgreSQL as a database, providing users the ability to track and predict sunset times. Leveraging the object-oriented nature of C# for a robust backend, React's declarative UI for a seamless user experience, and PostgreSQL's ACID compliance for data integrity, the application provides an intuitive interface for users to stay informed about sunset timings, enhancing their awareness of daylight transitions.

CONSTRUCTOR APPLICATION

https://github.com/huttnerdavid/codebusters

Constructor Application was developed by a team of three using C# (backend), React (frontend), and PostgreSQL (database), streamlining project oversight. Leveraging C#'s robust backend, React's dynamic frontend, and PostgreSQL's data integrity, the app enhances construction project monitoring. It provides insights into timelines, resource allocation and milestones, facilitating efficient project coordination.

EMPLOYEE TABLE

https://github.com/CodecoolGlobal/the-employee-madness-v2-react-Fonxy666

The Employee Table project is a solo-project using Express.js (backend), React (frontend), and MongoDB (database), adeptly manages company personnel. Leveraging Express.js for a robust backend, React for dynamic frontend, and MongoDB for flexible data storage, the app efficiently tracks office attendance, providing insights into staff presence for streamlined personnel management.

Work Experience

Semi-skilled Worker (2018 - 2023) — Mercedes Benz Manufacturing Hungary Kft. **Architect** (2017 - 2018) — Chudi és Társa Építőipari Kft.

Semi-skilled Worker (2015 - 2017) — Mercedes Benz Manufacturing Hungary Kft.

Education

Full-stack Developer (2023 - 2023) — Codecool Structural Architecture (2009 - 2015) — Gáspár András High School

Spoken Languages

Hungarian — Native **English** — Intermediate

